http://athletics.menlo.edu/privacy-policy/

MENUMENUSearchAboutMENLO COLLEGELand AcknowledgementVision and MissionFacts and StatsDiversity, Equity, InclusionStudent SuccessFind an ExpertMenlo DirectoryOur HistoryPoints of PrideRankings & ReviewsSafety & SecurityPresident's WelcomeMenlo College Celebrates 90th AnniversaryLEADERSHIPManagementBoard of TrusteesPresidentLOCATIONCompanies Near MenloLocation, Location, LocationMaps and DirectionsNEWS & PUBLICATIONSNewsNews & PublicationsThrough the GatesEVENTSEvents CalendarEvent ServicesAdmissions & Financial AidFIRST-YEAR STUDENTSTRANSFER STUDENTSINTERNATIONAL STUDENTSProspective StudentsCurrent StudentsVETERANSGUEST STUDENTSTUITION & FINANCIAL AIDFinancial AidNet Price CalculatorTuition & FeesScholarships & GrantsVISIT USMaps & DirectionsSchedule a VisitAdmissions EventsAPPLICATION DEADLINESNEWLY ADMITTED STUDENTSCONTACT USEnrollment StaffAcademicsACADEMICSAcademic CalendarMenlo College CatalogMAJORS & PROGRAMSAccounting Degree ProgramBusiness Analytics Degree ProgramEntrepreneurship and Innovation Degree ProgramFinance Degree ProgramHuman Resource Management Degree ProgramInternational Management Degree ProgramManagement Degree ProgramMarketing Degree ProgramPsychology Degree ProgramReal Estate Degree ProgramSports Management Degree ProgramONLINE TEACHINGePortfolioMenlo College Continuity of Education ResourcesMenlo College Online Teaching GuidelinesMenlo Online Learning EnvironmentHow to Use ZoomBowman Library Distance ServicesRecording and Privacy PolicyINTERNSHIPSFor Internship EmployersInternship Program for StudentsHandshakeIntern VoicesREQUIREMENTSFACULTYBOWMAN LIBRARYACADEMIC SUPPORT SERVICESAcademic CalendarFinal Examinations ScheduleAcademic AdvisingMath and Peer Tutoring CenterWriting & Oral Communication CenterTechnologyDisability ServicesSTUDY ABROADREGISTRARINNOVATION @ MENLOCOMMENCEMENTSUMMER SESSION 2020Executive EducationCENTERS OF STUDYEthics in Action Research and Education CenterRendanheyi Silicon Valley CenterWEBINAR SERIESStudent LifeBEYOND THE QUADCAMPUS LIFEClubs & OrganizationsStudent BodyStudent Government AssociationHousing & Residential LifeDining & Meal PlansResidence HallsResident AssistantsStudent-AthletesSERVSafety & SecurityMENLO ROOTSRESOURCESStudent AffairsCampus Resources – Hours of OperationFaith ResourcesHealth & WellnessImmigrant Information & ResourcesMental Health ServicesSocial Justice at Menlo CollegeDiversity, Equity, and InclusionTechnologyNEW STUDENT ORIENTATIONCAREER SERVICESStudent ServicesEmployer ServicesAlumni Career ServicesCareer Management CourseGraduate School PlanningMENLO OAK PRESSAthleticsMyMenloAlumniENGAGEWhat's NewAlumni Career ServicesAlumni ConnectionsEvents and ActivitiesUpdate Your InfoMenlo College Celebrates 90th AnniversaryIGNITEShare Your StoryHire an Oak!Alumni NotesIMPACTVolunteer OpportunitiesGive to MenloIn Honor of DorothyContact
Apply Now
GIVE A GIFT
QUICK LINKSCoronavirus Update Online Teaching Resources Academic Calendar Academic Catalog Events Calendar Conferences and Events Employment For the Media IT LibraryMaps and Directions Prospective Students Parents Virtual Bookstore Visit Campus Report a Campus Concern Report a Student Concern Request Information QUICK LINKS Privacy Policy Contact UsFor more information on how we collect and process your personal information, or if you have any questions or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@menlo.edu. Privacy PolicyYour privacy is very important to us. Menlo College is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and enjoyable web experience possible. This privacy policy is intended to inform you of how we collect information on our website, how we use the information that is collected, and how we protect any information that you choose to provide us.Information Collection and UseYou can visit the Menlo College website to read information about the College and our programs without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. The personal information we collect from our users at several different points on our website is outlined below.We do not share your personal data with any entity outside of Menlo College. We do not sell, rent or share your name, mailing address, email address or any other data that can personally identify you in any way to any outside group. Menlo College also complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which prohibits the release of most education records without student consent. All questions about FERPA or requests for student information should be forwarded to registrar@menlo.edu.Visitor BehaviorThe College uses tracking technologies to analyze trends and statistics related to site visitors in order to improve our website and the web experience. Information collected includes, but is not limited to: visitor IP address, pages visited on the site, date and time of the visit, referring site, browser used, and search terms used. Data from tracking technologies is not linked to a visitor’s personal information.CookiesCookies are pieces of information stored by your web browser on behalf of a website. Cookies may be used to track visitor behavior on our site, facilitate login to Menlo College email or other College-provided online services, and enable certain processes in the MyMenlo portal. If you prefer not to have cookies stored on your web browser, you may turn them off in your browser, or you may set your browser to ask you before accepting a new cookie; however, some pages may not function properly if the cookies are turned off. Cookies remain on your computer; we neither store cookies on our computers nor forward them to any external parties.LinksWe use email links on this site to allow you to contact us directly with any questions or comments that you may have. We read every message sent in, and try to reply promptly. We use the information collected to respond directly to your questions or comments.As a convenience to you, we sometimes provide links to other websites or resources. We do not control these sites and resources, do not endorse them, and are not responsible for their availability, content or delivery of services. In particular, external sites are not bound by Menlo’s online privacy policy; they may have their own policies or none at all.Voluntary InformationIn the course of using this website, you may choose to provide us with information to help us serve your needs. For example, you may send us email (through a mailer or a web form) to request information, you may sign up for a mailing list, or you may send us your address so we may send you an application or other material. Any personally identifiable information you send us will be used only for the purpose indicated. Requests for information will be directed to the appropriate staff to respond to the request, and may be recorded to help us update our site to better respond to similar requests.SecurityMenlo College has implemented generally accepted standards of technology security in order to protect information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Any sensitive or personal data that you enter on our website is transmitted in an encrypted form using a secure browser session (https). Data you enter during a visit to our site is stored on systems using the same security standards and procedures that protect our essential business data. Access to your data is restricted to authorized employees for Menlo College business purposes, and based on our employees’ need to know.International Transfer of Personal InformationPersonal information provided to us by users outside of the United States may be transferred to other countries, such as the United States, where data protection laws may differ from those of your home country. By providing us with your information, you acknowledge that your information will be transferred to the U.S. and processed on servers in the U.S. However, all reasonable steps will be taken to protect your privacy in accordance with the applicable data protection laws.EEA Data Subject RightsIf you are an individual located in the European Economic Area (EEA) only, you will have the following rights with regard to your personal data:Right of AccessYou may request details of your personal information that we hold. We will confirm whether we are processing your personal information and we will disclose supplementary information, including the categories of personal information, the sources from which it originated, the purpose and legal basis for the processing, the expected retention period, and the safeguards regarding personal information transfers to non-EEA countries, subject to the limitations set out in applicable statutes, regulations and other laws.Right of CorrectionWe will comply with your request to edit and update incorrect personal information promptly.Right to be ForgottenAt your request, we will delete your personal information promptly if:It is no longer necessary to retain your personal informationYou withdraw the consent which formed the basis of your personal information processingYou object to the processing of your personal information and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for such processingThe personal information was processed illegally; orThe personal information must be deleted for us to comply with our legal obligations We will decline your request for deletion if processing of your personal information is necessary:To comply with our legal obligationsIn pursuit of a legal actionTo detect and monitor fraud; orFor the performance of a task in the public interestRight to restrict processing of your personal informationAt your request, we will limit the processing of your personal information if:You dispute the accuracy of your personal informationYour personal information was processed unlawfully and you request a limitation on processing, rather than the deletion of your personal information;We no longer need to process your personal information, but you require your personal information in connection with a legal claim; orYou object to the processing pending verification as to whether an overriding legitimate ground for such processing exists.Right to NoticeIn so far as it is practicable, we will notify you of any correction, deletion, and/or limitation on the processing of your personal information.Right to data portabilityAt your request, we will provide you free-of-charge with your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format, if: (i) you provided us with personal information; (ii) the processing of your personal information is based on your consent or required for the performance of a contract; or (iii) the processing is carried out by automated means.Right to ObjectIf we process your personal information based upon our legitimate interest, then you have the right to object to this processing.Right Not to be Subject to DecisionsYou will not be subject to decisions with a legal or similarly significant effect (including profiling) that are based solely on the automated processing of your personal information, unless you have given us your explicit consent or where they are necessary for a contract with us.Right to Withdraw ConsentYou have the right to withdraw any consent you may have previously given us at any time. If you withdraw your consent, this will not affect the lawfulness of our collecting, or using and sharing of your personal information up to the point in time that you withdraw your consent. Even if you withdraw your consent, we may still use your information that has been fully anonymized and does not personally identify you.Right to complain to a Supervisory AuthorityIf you are not satisfied with our response, you have the right to complain to or seek advice from a supervisory authority and/or bring a claim against us in any court of competent jurisdiction.If you wish to contact us in connection with the exercise of your rights listed above, please email us at privacy@menlo.edu.
We will respond to your written request without unreasonable delay and in accordance with any deadlines imposed by law. Unless we notify you at the time of your request, we will not charge you any fee in connection with the exercise of your rights.Policy ChangesWe reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this policy periodically for changes. Menlo College1000 El Camino RealAtherton, CA 94027-4301800-55-MENLOadmissions@menlo.eduMenlo Security Services© Menlo College Menlo Directory Conferences & Events Services Contact Us Request Info Apply Now Transfer Students Schedule a Visit Maps & Directions For the Media Jobs Privacy Policy Feedback Virtual Bookstore Menlo Apparel Store Social Media Directory Support Menlo with Your Gift! Sitemap
Join us on Facebook
Follow us on Instagram
Follow us on Twitter
See us on YouTube
Connect with us on LinkedIn Do NOT follow this link or you will be banned from the site!
MENUMenlo CollegeSearchAboutMENLO COLLEGELand AcknowledgementVision and MissionFacts and StatsDiversity, Equity, InclusionStudent Success BackFind an ExpertMenlo DirectoryOur HistoryPoints of PrideRankings & ReviewsSafety & SecurityPresident’s WelcomeMenlo College Celebrates 90th Anniversary BackLEADERSHIPManagementBoard of TrusteesPresident BackLOCATIONCompanies Near MenloLocation, Location, LocationMaps and Directions BackNEWS & PUBLICATIONSNewsNews & PublicationsThrough the Gates BackEVENTSEvents CalendarEvent Services Back BackAdmissions & Financial AidFIRST-YEAR STUDENTSTRANSFER STUDENTSINTERNATIONAL STUDENTSProspective StudentsCurrent Students BackVETERANSGUEST STUDENTSTUITION & FINANCIAL AIDFinancial AidNet Price CalculatorTuition & FeesScholarships & Grants BackVISIT USMaps & DirectionsSchedule a VisitAdmissions Events BackAPPLICATION DEADLINESNEWLY ADMITTED STUDENTSCONTACT USEnrollment Staff Back BackAcademicsMAJORS & PROGRAMSAccounting Degree ProgramBusiness Analytics Degree ProgramEntrepreneurship and Innovation Degree ProgramFinance Degree ProgramHuman Resource Management Degree ProgramInternational Management Degree ProgramManagement Degree ProgramMarketing Degree ProgramPsychology Degree ProgramReal Estate Degree ProgramSports Management Degree Program BackONLINE TEACHINGePortfolioMenlo College Continuity of Education ResourcesMenlo College Online Teaching GuidelinesMenlo Online Learning EnvironmentHow to Use ZoomBowman Library Distance ServicesRecording and Privacy Policy BackINTERNSHIPSFor Internship EmployersInternship Program for StudentsHandshakeIntern Voices BackREQUIREMENTSFACULTYBOWMAN LIBRARYACADEMIC SUPPORT SERVICESAcademic CalendarFinal Examinations ScheduleAcademic AdvisingMath and Peer Tutoring CenterWriting & Oral Communication CenterTechnologyDisability Services BackSTUDY ABROADREGISTRARINNOVATION @ MENLOCOMMENCEMENTSUMMER SESSION 2020 BackExecutive EducationCENTERS OF STUDYEthics in Action Research and Education CenterRendanheyi Silicon Valley Center BackWEBINAR SERIES BackStudent LifeBEYOND THE QUADCAMPUS LIFEClubs & OrganizationsStudent BodyStudent Government Association BackHousing & Residential LifeDining & Meal PlansResidence HallsResident Assistants BackStudent-AthletesSERVSafety & Security BackMENLO ROOTSRESOURCESStudent AffairsCampus Resources – Hours of OperationFaith ResourcesHealth & WellnessImmigrant Information & ResourcesMental Health ServicesSocial Justice at Menlo CollegeDiversity, Equity, and Inclusion BackTechnology BackNEW STUDENT ORIENTATIONCAREER SERVICESStudent ServicesEmployer ServicesAlumni Career ServicesCareer Management CourseGraduate School Planning BackMENLO OAK PRESS BackAthleticsMyMenloAlumniENGAGEWhat’s NewAlumni Career ServicesAlumni ConnectionsEvents and ActivitiesUpdate Your InfoMenlo College Celebrates 90th Anniversary BackIGNITEShare Your StoryHire an Oak!Alumni Notes BackIMPACTVolunteer OpportunitiesGive to MenloIn Honor of Dorothy Back BackContact
× Close Panel
